// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is marketing?",
    answer: "All of above",
    options: [
      "Marketing is not about promotion or advertising only",
      "Marketing is complex topic or a concept",
      "This is used to make a comprehensive plan of action to generate leads, increase sales, increase brand awareness or acquire more customers",
      "All of above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Effective marketing requires?",
    answer: "All of above",
    options: [
      "Careful planning",
      "Creative approaches",
      "Smart execution",
      "All of above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "It’s used by marketer to attract people who perform searches that imply they’re interested in learning about a particular industry?",
    answer: "Search engine optimization",
    options: [
      "Search engine optimization",
      "Print marketing",
      "Social media marketing",
      "Video marketing"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Digital marketing also known as?",
    answer: "Both",
    options: [
      "Internet Marketing",
      "Online Marketing",
      "Both",
      "None"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which marketing use the online platform to promote the product and services of our company.",
    answer: "Online marketing",
    options: [
      "Traditional marketing",
      "Online marketing",
      "Both",
      "None"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "SEO is most important part of which marketing?",
    answer: "Digital marketing",
    options: [
      "Digital marketing",
      "Online marketing",
      "Traditional Marketing",
      "None"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "SMS marketing can very effective for real estate, ----------- And ----------------.",
    answer: "Education and healthcare business",
    options: [
      "Colleges and university.",
      "Education and society",
      "Collage and student",
      "Education and healthcare business"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Content marketing is a digital marketing strategy where marketing is done using-----------.",
    answer: "Both",
    options: [
      "High –quality",
      "Relevant content",
      "Both",
      "None"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Marketing automation is future of ---------?",
    answer: "Email marketing",
    options: [
     " Social media marketing ",
      "Email marketing", 
      "SMS marketing ",
      "Search engine marketing ",

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the 5 Ds Digital marketing?",
    answer: "All three",
    options: [
      "Device, platform",
      "Data, media", 
      "Data, technology",
      "All three", 

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "------------------ is the second largest search engine after Google.",
    answer: "YouTube",
    options: [
      "Facebook",
      "Instagram",
      "YouTube",
      "Twitter",
 

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "----------------- is when the marketing activities are undertaken in a conventional fashion",
    answer: "Traditional marketing",
    options: [
      "Digital marketing",
      "Traditional marketing",
      "Both",
      "None",
      

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "----------------------- is method of paying to post sponsored.",
    answer: "Instagram",
    options: [
     "Instagram",
      "Facebook",
      "YouTube",
      "Twitter",
      

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "E-mail marketing is a very effective medium for------------------.",
    answer: "Communication",
    options: [
      "Automation", 
      "Communication", 
      "Automation & communication",
     " None",
      

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Instagram is part of the ----------- network only",
    answer: "Facebook",
    options: [
      "Twitter", 
      "Facebook",
      "YouTube", 
      "LinkIn",


    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 16,
    question: "In ------------, 120 million instagrammers visited a website , got direction , called , emailed, or direct messaged to learn about a business based on an Instagram ad",
    answer: "March 2017",
    options: [
      "March 2018",
      "March 2015",
      "March 2017",
      "March 2016",



    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 17,
    question: "-------------- Creating and publishing all kinds of videos that entertain and educate their core customer",
    answer: "Video marketing",
    options: [
      "Search engine marketing", 
      "Print marketing",
      "Video marketing", 
      "Blog marketing",  



    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 18,
    question: "----------- are no longer exclusive to the individual writer.",
    answer: "Blog",
    options: [
      "Blog",
      "Print",
      "Video",
      "Internet",



    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 19,
    question: "SEO is part of inbound marketing and ------------------------.",
    answer: "Search engine marketing",
    options: [
      "Print marketing" ,
     "Search engine marketing",
      "Email marketing" ,
      "SMS marketing" ,
      


    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 20,
    question: "According to Instagram, ---------- of people say they discover new products on the platform.",
    answer: "60%",
    options: [
      "80%",
      "45%",
     "60%",
      "100%",



    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];